Thanks for sharing the table with me. To think all the other patrons are actually avoiding me. Hmph. I'll remember this
Gracias por compartir la mesa conmigo. Y pensar que los demás clientes me están evitando... ¡Hum! Me acordaré de esto.
Seriously... They care that much about my lineage? Even if I were out for vengeance, they'd have to wait their turn
De verdad... ¿Tanto les importa mi linaje? Aunque deseara vengarme, tendrían que esperar su turno.
The Gunnhildr clan, the Ragnvindr clan, and the Lawrence clan are the three most prominent families in Mondstadt's history
Los Gunnhildr, los Ragnvindr y los Lawrence son las tres familias más importantes de la historia de Mondstadt.
Among them, the Lawrence clan became blinded by their desires, plunging Mondstadt into a dark era under the aristocracy's oppression
Entre ellas, la familia Lawrence, cegada por sus deseos, arrastró a Mondstadt hacia una era oscura dominada por la opresión aristocrática.
In time, Lady Vennessa overthrew the aristocracy and established the Knights of Favonius while the Lawrence clan quickly fell into obscurity
Más tarde, Vennessa derrocó a la aristocracia y estableció los Caballeros de Favonius, mientras que los Lawrence se sumieron rápidamente en la oscuridad.
Over the next thousand years, their flame of vengeance continued to flicker and burn, but never again did it ignite into a blaze
Durante los siguientes mil años, el fuego de su venganza no dejó de titilar, pero ya nunca más ardió con tanta fuerza.
Perhaps the finishing blow to the Lawrence clan was...
Quizás el golpe final para la familia Lawrence fue...
She who is known as the "Spindrift Knight," most gifted descendant of the Lawrence clan, Eula, joining the Knights of Favonius
que Eula, la descendiente más talentosa de los Lawrence, se uniera a los Caballeros de Favonius.
Although the word "vengeance" is always upon her lips, she has proved time and again that she is a kindhearted and honorable ally
Aunque ella siempre habla de "venganza", ha demostrado una y otra vez que es una aliada honorable y de buen corazón.
Hey, when a noblewoman is speaking, you are to lower your drink and look her directly in the eyes. You really ought to learn some proper etiquette...
Oye, cuando una mujer noble está hablando, debes bajar tu bebida y mirarla directamente a los ojos. En serio, deberías aprender un poco de protocolo...
Achoo! Oh, I bet it's that Gunnhildr girl talking about me behind my back again...
¡Achís! Oh, apuesto a que esa Gunnhildr está hablando de mí a mis espaldas otra vez...
Hmph! Mark my words... vengeance will be mine!
¡Hum! Recuérdenlo bien... ¡la venganza será mía!